## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a front end developer from Winchester, Virginia. I come from a design background and have a passion for great design and I love building user interfaces. My specialty lies in creating UX focused and shiny Uls.

I create and style user interfaces for web and mobile applications. I've worked with several front end frameworks including React, Angular, Ionic, and Ext IS.

On a typical night you can find me advancing my education in JavaScript, game programming, or playing Dungeons and Dragons.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - Present, Front End Developer

I am currently working as a contractor for **Fiat Insight** where I am building a custom scheduling application in React JS, implemented inside a WordPress theme and utilizing the new WP API.

## 2014 - 2016, UI Engineer

At Modus Create I worked (mostly) remotely as a user interface engineer in a lean and agile environment. I built user interfaces, templates, and components for applications in Angular JS, Ionic, and Ext JS. I collaborated with UX designers, clients, project managers, and other engineers. I am comfortable working in a fast-paced environment with daily standups, Jira/Pivotal Tracker workflows and tickets, and constant communication via Slack or video chat.

## 2012 - 2014, UI Designer

I was a user interface designer at **Timberlake Membership Software** where I did responsive web design. I built responsive websites using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap which were integrated with a custom ASP content management system.

## **REFERENCES**

Jay Garcia, CTO jay@moduscreate.com 301-785-6030

Pat Sheridan, CEO pat@moduscreate.com 571-241-8580

## AT A GLANCE

Modus Create Inc From 2014 to 2016. User Interface Engineer Timberlake Membership Software From 2012 to 2014. User Interface Designer Immerge Technologies From 2011 to 2012.

Web Designer / Game Artist

## **EDUCATION**

BFA, Computer Game Design George Mason University Fairfax, VA 22030

# SKILLS AND OTHER THINGS

In order of a strange concoction of self-described knowledge and experience:

0	HTML
0	CSS —
0	Sass
0	Sketch/Photoshop/Illustrator

Themes Responsive Design Grids Flexbox Material Design

JavaScript

- Angular JS
- Ionic
- React JS
- Gulp
- Webpack
- Git

2014 Winner of Lean Startup Machine in Washington, DC -BoozeBox, a subscription box of personally catered craft beers delivered to your door.